[GRUNTS] Oh!
[STATIC CRACKLING]
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING]
[NOISEMAKER BLAATS]
[SHRIEKING]
[STATIC CRACKLING]
[CANNED LAUGHTER]
Well. Chief. what's all
the excitement about?
- Hodgkins.
- Yes. sir.
Activate the Cone of Silence.
The Cone of Silence?
[WHIRRING]
[CANNED LAUGHTER]
How much do you know about KAOS?
There he is.
- Thank you. Lori.
- Mm-hmm.
Looking good. Pops.
How you doing?
Marla called.
Marla called?
Your cousin Marla?
Marla.
Is that so?
Hey. Alice just told me
you guys were talking
about Mack's new school.
Remember?
We're moving so your
granddaughter. Makayla.
she can go to that new
school she got into.
It's a real big deal.
We're all real excited about it.
You're selling the house?
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Yeah. yeah. got a great buyer.
It's a young family with kids.
And we haven't picked a new place yet.
But I'm gonna bring those pictures...
I... I... I never agreed. [STAMMERS]
Well. we talked about it.
You look like my son.
That's right. Dad. It's me.
It's Adam.
I'm right here.
You're... you're moving.
Do we have... we have a lot
of memories in our house.
Yeah. I... no. I never agreed.
I never agreed. No. I never.
- Hey. it's okay.
- I never!
Dad. I understand. I understand.
We don't have to do anything right now.
It's okay.
- We don't?
- No. no. everything's so good.
Hey. we got plenty of time.
He said that cousin Marla called.
Marla. who died of
blood cancer five years ago?
He forgot about the move.
so he got upset again.
I don't know.
Maybe I should stop trying to connect.
I'm sorry.
It is what it is.
Yeah.
Mack. come here for a sec.
Check this out.
So these are mine.
You should see if there's
anything you want.
There might be some cool stuff in there.
Your old toys?
They're not old. They're vintage.
There might be collectibles in there.
Right.
Old.
Over-under on when
she jumps on that iPad?
30 seconds.
Are you really gonna
watch every one of those?
There might be
unmarked home videos in here.
Those things are gold. Come on.
But...
This is important stuff here.
[STATIC CRACKLING]
This look like a TV show to you?
[INDISTINCT VOICES]
[MICROPHONE CRACKLING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
What the hell was that?
I don't know.
♪ ♪
Jesus.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
[STATIC CRACKLING]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
[LAUGHS]
Pops. why is this funny?
Those guys.
Dad. hey.
I need you to think
about what we just saw.
Okay?
This is the sleeve that
I found the tape in at home.
That's your handwriting. See?
Do you remember writing this?
Is it. like. from a case or something?
'Cause that looks like
an evidence label. right?
Is that why this was at the house?
Fake. You can't fool me.
I'm not trying to fool you.
Who are these guys?
Who's trying to fool you?
Dad. this is a homicide. right?
Did detectives try and work this?
Is that why you had it at home?
When are you taking me home?
This is your home. Dad.
You lived here for. like. a year now.
It's a nice room.
Yeah. yeah. we got you the best.
[WHISTLE TRILLS]
Which one's your grandson?
Number 58.
Let's see some checking out there. 58!
Come on!
Hey. so I found an evidence
videotape in my dad's stuff
in our basement.
There's no RD or inventory number.
It was a guy slicing another
guy's throat in a motel room.
Evidence label and time stamp say 2019.
Seriously? Bob kept that video?
Okay. so you know about it?
Oh. kid. yeah.
Yeah. I do.
The guys called it
the 2019 Motel Massacre.
But it's a prank.
A prank?
We were always pranking
each other back then.
You're kidding me.
That's... that's not real?
As far as I know it wasn't.
Well. who sent it?
Nobody fessed up.
It was sent anonymously to Bob.
Bob took it pretty seriously. though.
dug up leads for about a month.
They never get anywhere.
There's never anywhere to get.
That one went too far.
I'm sorry. Adam.
Bob deserved better.
I don't know. man.
That didn't look fake to me. Mick.
I mean. the splatter pattern
looked real.
I don't know what to say.
I mean. maybe. maybe we got it wrong.
Hey. 58. start hitting somebody!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Prank my ass.
[GARBLED SPEECH]
Bumper to bumper. all of Pulaski.
Pulaski. Pulaski. Pulaski.
♪ ♪
You've reached Kim.
Please leave a message.
Hey. it's me.
I think you guys are probably in bed.
I'm gonna follow up on my dad's video.
So it's probably gonna be a bit late.
I love you. I'll see you in the morning.
[DISTANT SIRENS WAILING]
Hello.
Can I help you?
Yeah. I need a room.
79 bucks up front.
All right.
Hey. is room 7 available?
I'd like to be close to the pop machine.
Yeah. we have almost
everything in there.
You having a party?
- No. no. it's just me.
- Good.
We have families here.
I need some ID.
Mr. Redmond. man with the cash.
All right.
You know about the pop machine.
We got snack machines
on the second floor.
Sandwiches ain't half bad.
Thank you. Good to know.
Yep.
Okay.
[VOICES SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
It's not just the toilet!
- It's the goddamn sink!
- Okay.
Settle down. We're on it!
Well. well. well.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[GRUNTS] Oh!
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[GASPS]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[EARS RINGING]
[VOICE ECHOING] Hello?
[GROANS]
[GROANING]
Oh. son of a bitch.
[SIGHS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
What the hell?
Adam?
No. you can't be up
walking around right now.
Come on. Gotta get back in the bed.
What's going on?
- Are you okay?
- What the hell's going on?
- Are you feeling okay?
- Yeah.
You were out all night.
I mean. how are you feeling?
My head?
Yeah. I know.
You're at the hospital. all right?
Yeah. I know. Are you all right?
What happened? How'd I get here?
You don't remember?
No.
Where's Mack?
Okay. listen.
It's okay.
Doctors have already
done all their tests.
So you are all right.
They think you were hit
on the back of the head
with a blunt object.
And you have a concussion.
Babe. you have a really bad concussion.
But the MRI shows no internal bleeding.
It shows no brain damage.
So you're gonna be all right. okay?
Take that hand.
- Oh. that's good.
- Yeah.
What happened?
I don't...
I don't know. Adam.
You left me a message at 9:30 last night
saying you were following up
on your dad's thing.
What... what do you mean?
Bob's videotape. the one
we found at the house?
Yeah. all right.
- Okay.
An hour later. you were found
by a civilian
in an alley off LaSalle.
You were unconscious.
and you were a block away from your car.
So the car. they can...
- Yeah.
- They know where I came from.
No. OCD techs are...
are having trouble. Do you want water?
With the car's historical data.
something about. like.
a tech upgrade or something.
All right. They found me on LaSalle?
Yes. LaSalle.
How did you get there?
Do you know. like. how you were attacked
or why you were attacked?
Do you remember anything?
Adam. do you remember any detail?
I don't remember anything at all.
No. I'm not worried about memory loss.
It's rather common for a TBI.
It may feel like memories are jumbled.
shuffled around for a bit.
I know a little about memory loss.
His father has Alzheimer's.
Mm-hmm. Look here.
Well. this is very different.
Only your short-term memory is affected.
And that will likely come back in time.
The confusion will go away as well.
I'm sure you're right. doc.
I just... I would love to talk
to a specialist about it.
Adam. Dr. Patel is the brain specialist.
Right.
- Squeeze.
- Sorry.
Is there anything I can do
to make the memory come back quicker?
There are some memory
exercises in the pamphlet.
But rest is best.
I need to keep you for a couple
more days to make sure
there's no latent swelling.
So just take it easy for me. okay?
It's the only thing that you need to do.
Thank you.
Everything's looking good.
- I heard her.
- Okay. good.
Thank you. Doctor.
[TENSE MUSIC]
[GRUNTS] Oh.
- Don't tell Mom.
- Stop bothering me.
- Love you. Bye.
- Stop.
Don't tell Mom.
What'd you find?
Are you guys doing okay?
I just wanna know what you found.
We got Adam's Jeep
on a traffic cam at 9:23 p.m.
headed southbound on Fuller.
Oh. that's just before
he left me that voicemail.
Yes. and we have footage that shows him
turning eastbound on West 74th Street.
And there's no PODs there.
but we did find a
Crestline Motel on that block.
We think it's a match for
the room in the murder tape.
We're headed there now to check it out.
Platt notified Voight.
He's still out of state
testifying in court.
Copy. I'm gonna do some digging here.
- Keep me updated. all right?
- Will do.
Okay.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Can I help you?
[GRUNTS]
I think you might be in the wrong room.
Who are you?
You don't remember?
No. no. I don't.
We know each other?
We met yesterday.
♪ ♪
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Hey. sweetie.
You think I could steal a chair?
- Mm-hmm. Go ahead.
- Um...
[CHUCKLES] Uh. I'll get it.
I'll follow you. how's that?
Bless you.
Thank you.
[LAUGHS]
That's good?
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
5021 Eddie. emergency.
I have a male. white. slender.
5'9". jean jacket. dark pants.
Wanted for the attempted murder
of a Chicago Police officer.
Last seen on the fourth floor
of St. Luke's.
Send me cars.
10-4. 5021 Eddie.
We have cars coming your way.
♪ ♪
Adam. Adam!
- Oh. my God!
- You all right?
Are you okay? Are you all right?
- Hey.
- Was a man just here?
Skinny. jean jacket. brown hair.
Left when the nurse did the rounds.
What did he want?
He said he was the one who found
me unconscious. Called the ambulance.
He didn't find you unconscious.
A woman found you unconscious. Damn it!
You... you don't leave him alone.
5021 Eddie. Squad.
- Have any units found this guy?
- That's a negative. Eddie.
We have two 9th District
cars headed your way.
Get them here fast.
He's targeting one of us.
- Kim. you got ears?
- Copy. 5021 Eddie.
Go. go. go.
Crestline Motel's the spot.
Looks like the manager wired
the rooms with cameras.
He dumped some of the evidence.
but there's cables
leading back to the rooms.
The guy's a peeping Tom.
You're talking about Dan Boyer?
Yeah. he's nowhere to be found.
No. he's here at St. Luke's.
Adam must have found his cameras
and he attacked him.
I need any available units
to get here now.
I need backup.
Dan Boyer. Chicago PD!
Chicago PD!
♪ ♪
Boyer. stop!
- [SIREN CHIRPS]
- Drop your weapon!
I'm police! I'm police!
- Drop it!
- Freeze!
Get his gun! Get his gun!
Got it.
Stay down!
You just made things
a lot harder for yourself.
No. no. I didn't touch him.
You didn't hit him on the head?
- No.
- No?
Then why'd you come to the
hospital if not to finish the job?
I checked him into the motel.
I didn't know he was a cop.
I saw later that he had found my...
Illegal cameras?
Security devices.
But he never came back to the motel.
I ran his plates.
I got a lot of friends in the CPD.
- and they're always...
- Hey.
Why'd you come to the hospital?
To make an arrangement. financial one.
Done it before with the blue.
But he didn't remember anything.
so I figured. you know.
bank error in my favor.
I never done anything to him.
How long have you been recording people?
What's that got to do with anything?
You recognize that?
I don't know.
You don't kn... do you
tape a lot of homicides?
- No.
- Is that you with a knife?
- No. Hell no.
- Then who is it?
I have no idea.
I wasn't working that day.
I don't know.
I didn't see the tape
until after. way after.
The room was empty by then.
It was cleaned.
We don't keep receipts.
You didn't send the tape to police?
No. no. of course not. I got rid of it.
I don't know how you got this.
but that's not me on the tape.
I haven't hurt anybody.
Have it your way.
I will find out if you are lying.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Let's clear this corner. Joe. with me.
Hey. Shannon.
It's definitely blood.
Find out whose it is.
DNA matches Joe Verlaine.
It confirms he was
the victim on the tape.
In 2019. he would have been 33.
All right. Did you notify the family?
He doesn't have any.
He did two tours in Iraq.
Honorably discharged
with a taste for ketamine.
Now. according to his arrest reports.
the drug helped him cope with his PTSI.
Joe Verlaine was a drifter.
He has arrests for possession
in three or four different states.
Anyone heard from this guy since 2019?
No. but in 2019. the Crestline Motel
was a known spot to score ketamine.
Okay. so what. the murder was
just a drug deal gone wrong?
No?
Yeah. that's our working theory.
I was thinking maybe this might
unlock something for you.
maybe something at the motel.
something you were investigating there?
Anything?
[EARS RINGING]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
I don't know.
I just don't know anything.
I wanna help. I just... I can't.
That's okay. It's okay.
We'll keep digging. and...
I'm gonna keep trying.
Okay.
Thank you. honey.
Drug deal gone wrong
at the Crestline Motel.
John Verlaine. the Crestline Motel.
John Verla... no.
Come on. Adam.
Joe Verlaine.
Joe Verlaine was honorably discharged.
had a taste for ketamine.
Dan Boyer.
Joe Verlaine. Dan Boyer.
It's a drug deal gone wrong.
Must have known each other somehow.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Okay. just walk through your day. man.
Just walk through your day.
Packing boxes.
going through home videos.
going through...
going through all Dad's tapes.
Saw the murder.
Went to see Dad.
Went to see Dad. went to see Dad.
Something happened after you went...
crazy.
This is crazy.
Ah!
How could I not remember anything?
Okay. so let's walk through this.
So you're leaving the house.
You grab your jacket.
Keys. jacket. wallet. keys.
Notebook. wallet. phone.
Drove to see Dad
to show... to show him the...
the murder tape.
Jacket. keys. notebook. phone.
Put the phone in my pocket.
Jacket. keys. notebook. wallet.
Drove to see Dad.
Notebook.
♪ ♪
Okay. okay.
Knows car.
Oh. my God.
There has to be something else here.
That cannot be it.
Knows car.
What the hell does that mean. man?
[PHONE BUZZING]
Hey. Alice.
Wait. how is he doing?
How bad?
I'm glad you could come by
on such short notice.
I'll leave you two to it.
I'll see you before
the end of my shift. Bob.
Thank you. Alice.
Dad...
You have to eat.
Listen to me. Now. you have to eat.
Pops.
[EXHALES]
Dad.
[GROANS]
[SIGHS]
[TENSE MUSIC]
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING]
♪ ♪
We're on it!
Chicago PD. Where's the manager?
I... I... I don't know.
- You know about this?
- I... I have to go back to work.
Hey. Hey. man.
Slow down. slow down.
You're not in trouble.
All right?
You work maintenance here?
What's your name?
Carlos.
How long have you worked here. Carlos?
I promise you. you're not in trouble.
Ten years.
Okay. so you worked here in 2019?
Yeah?
- Right?
- Yes.
- Please. I have to go.
- Hey. listen.
Slow down. Slow down.
I just... I wanna ask you
a few questions about a tape.
Okay?
I swear on my daughter.
I just fix things.
I fix things. and I go home.
Please. I have to go.
Hey. Hey. Listen.
Hey. hey. hey. who put the cameras?
- I don't know.
- Was it the manager?
It's my boss.
Please. I need this job.
Okay. I understand. Just look.
What's your last name?
Carlos.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Carlos!
Carlos.
Stop running!
Ah. come on.
[GRUNTS] Oh!
[GROANING]
Kim. listen.
I wasn't attacked. okay?
It was an accident.
Wait. what do you mean? You remember?
Yeah. I was chasing a
guy from the Crestline Motel.
Uh. guy's name is Carlos.
He works maintenance. He knew something.
I spooked him. but I could tell
he knew something.
Okay. run all motel employee
records from the Crestline.
And you're sure that he's not
the offender from the tape?
No. no. Stats don't match.
All right. We're on it. Adam.
And you stay at the hospital. okay?
No. I'm coming to you.
- Thanks. Jason.
- Yeah.
No. no. no. you were
not cleared for discharge.
- Hey. You find him?
- You cannot be here right now.
I know. honey. I know.
But did you... did you find him?
- Yes.
- Yeah?
Yes. we got him. He's in our custody.
All right.
His full name is Carlos Gonzalez.
He worked at the motel
for over a decade.
We got a maid to tell us his name.
That's him. right?
- That's him.
- Good.
It looks like Boyer has been paying
Gonzalez under the table.
and that could explain
why he ran from you.
Why under the table?
He has an active warrant on him.
failure to appear
on a felony theft charge.
This guy's been laying low
for a long time.
Okay.
I remember you.
We were about to talk about 2019.
about a homicide
that was caught on tape.
You got scared.
We don't care about your active warrant.
We can actually help with that.
You knew about the tapes. didn't you?
That there was a murder caught on one?
Carlos.
Did you send a tape
of the murder to a...
a patrol officer in 2019?
If you did. that officer. he's my dad.
He tried to work the case.
Your father is Officer Bob Ruzek?
Yes. yeah.
You know him?
Yeah. he... he pulled me over
about ten years ago
for a busted tail light.
And. uh. that was it.
I... I was going to jail.
I told him about my wife.
She... she has epilepsy.
She... she can't work.
She needs medicine. She...
she needs me. You know?
You understand?
I... I couldn't go to prison.
I can't go to prison.
So your dad. he... he just let me go.
And I never forgot that.
[SOFT MUSIC]
And the tape?
That murder caught on camera?
You knew about Boyer's hidden cameras.
When I saw the tape and that
guy getting killed. I...
I made a copy.
And you sent it to my dad.
He's a decent man.
Carlos...
Can you ID the person on the tape?
- Oh. no.
- Listen to me.
Hey. listen.
That warrant. we can make a deal.
You won't have the warrant
hanging over your head anymore.
Please.
♪ ♪
That guy. he comes around
the motel and sell drugs.
- Everybody knew him.
- Okay.
A name. Carlos. We just need a name.
I don't have a name.
I'm sorry.
All I know is what they called him.
- They called him Voodoo.
- Voodoo?
That's all I know. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
That... no. don't be sorry.
That helps.
Thank you.
We ran the alias Voodoo through CHRIS.
We got multiple hits.
Three dead. two in prison.
Leaves us with three viable
matches for the killer.
except only one of them
matched the description
given to us by Carlos
and the video stats.
And that's this guy. Mark Knight. 32.
busted back in 2022 for ketamine distro.
Sentenced to two years.
got out after one.
And the night Verlaine was killed.
Mark Knight's cell phone was
connected to the Crestline Wi-Fi.
So it puts him at the scene.
but it's not enough
to connect him to the murder.
Carlos said he saw Voodoo
putting a large suitcase
into the trunk
of his car. a gray hatchback.
- Hatchback. Yeah.
- That can't be a coincidence.
Back in 2019. Mark Knight
had a silver 2010 Toyota Matrix
registered in his name.
That's good. We know where he is now?
Uh. he could be at his LKA.
951 South Kedvale Avenue.
Narcotics thinks it's a stash house.
- Platt. can you crack off a...
- Yeah. I'll work on a warrant.
All right. let's move.
No. no. no. no.
You're no good to anyone
on the street if you cannot...
Jesus. Kim. I'll ride your hip.
Just. I have to do this for my dad.
What day is it?
Wednesday.
What'd you give to Mack in those boxes?
- My old toys.
- Where did you propose to me?
- Which time?
- Last time.
On the edge of the bed. You loved it.
You know I could've gotten
the last question right...
Oh. just let me have that.
You're with me the whole time.
Adam. the whole time.
[TENSE MUSIC]
We got a positive.
We got confirmed visual of Mark Knight
entering 25 minutes ago. He's home.
But it's unclear if he's alone or not.
Copy that. Hold the back.
We're moving now.
- You good?
- Let's go.
♪ ♪
We're breaching.
BOTH: Chicago PD!
Police! Gun!
Stay down. Stay down.
Adam. I got him. I got him.
Hands behind your back. Let's go!
Mark Knight.
you're under arrest for
the murder of Joe Verlaine.
Hey. go home.
Hey. Alice.
How's he doing?
Hey.
Tact team's gonna sit on the place.
wait for Forensics to arrive.
We'll get started booking Knight.
Okay. good.
You good on the paper?
Yeah.
[YAWNS]
I gotta tell you. Dad.
I just got the smallest window into
what you've been going through.
how hard this must have been for you...
How strong you've been.
I love you. Dad.
Very much.
And I want you to know that...
I'm gonna remember everything.
I'm gonna remember everything
for the both of us.
So...
it's okay.
You can let go.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[EXHALES]
Look at this guy.
He's legit.
Yeah! Great shot. 33!
[NOISEMAKER BLAATS]
Careful. Adam.
All right. now. blow out the candles.
- Wow!
- Did you see that?
Did you see how high I got?
I did! That was amazing!
Oh. my gosh. you're flying.
You wanna really fly?
- You wanna really fly?
- [SHRIEKING]
All right. I'm gonna get you.
Go on. I'm gonna get you.
I'm gonna get you. I'm gonna get you.
I'm gonna...
♪ ♪
[EXHALES]
[WOLF HOWLS]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-